<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinko Apps</title>
    <link>https://apps.sinko.me/en/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sinko Apps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Dmytrii Sinko</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 13:20:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://apps.sinko.me/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://apps.sinko.me/en/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 13:20:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.sinko.me/en/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In this privacy policy we describe what kind of data we may collect of you in connection with your use of our applications, websites and related services and how we may use such data. Below we call these collectively “Services”. By using our Services, you agree to the processing of your data in accordance with this privacy policy.
We may amend this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version online so please review it frequently. Your continued use of our Services after the posting of a new version is deemed as your acceptance of the modified terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-data-do-we-collect-and-why&#34;&gt;What data do we collect and why?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal data.&lt;/strong&gt; We do not collect personal data that identifies you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analytics data.&lt;/strong&gt; We use analytical services and other tools (such as Flurry and Google Analytics) on areas of our Services which enable us to collect your IP address or other identifier, usage data relating to our Services as well as information on your device properties. Based on this data we may create statistics, provide better services to our customers as well as analyze and further develop our Services. We treat this information as non-personal data.
You can opt out of the Flurry Analytics tracking and personalized ads/recommendations from Flurry by clicking &lt;a href=&#34;https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and you can disable Google Analytics with &lt;a href=&#34;https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout&#34;&gt;this add-on tool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ad serving.&lt;/strong&gt; We and our partners may use ad serving technology to provide advertisements of interest to you within the Services (for example within the Android application). In this connection we and our partners may collect and use information about you, such as your Service session activity, device identifier, MAC address, IMEI, coarse geo-location information and IP address. Please note that our partners operate under their own privacy policies.
For more information, see
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/&lt;/a&gt; about Admob&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may also see our own advertisements in other services. If you click such advertisements and install our application, we may share a device identifier with the advertiser to verify installs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cookies and other identifiers.&lt;/strong&gt; We and our partners may use cookies and other identifiers (such as clear gifs or pixel tags). With cookies and other identifiers we and our partners can provide a better user experience. You may delete the cookies from your device after using our Services. If you disable cookies on your browser, some parts of our Services may not function properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-security-and-sharing&#34;&gt;Data security and sharing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data security.&lt;/strong&gt; All of your data is protected in accordance with generally acceptable industry standards and although no system is 100 % secure, we take reasonable steps to safeguard your data from unauthorized access. We may use partners and contractors to process data for us in accordance with this privacy policy and in such cases we take steps to ensure that your data is kept secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data sharing.&lt;/strong&gt; We may publish aggregated or de-personalised data based on our users’ information (such as statistics) provided that such information does not identify you.
We may process your data outside the country where you live in (for example if you are an EU citizen, outside the EU or the European Economic Area). This can happen if, for instance, the service provider of our analytical services is located outside your country. In such cases, we will take steps to ensure that your personal data is processed lawfully and in accordance with this privacy policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;external-links&#34;&gt;External links&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Services may contain links to external sites, such as Facebook and Youtube and link content from external third party sources. Please note that the use of such third party sites or content is subject to the privacy policies and usage terms of the third party in question instead of our own terms and we do not have control or assume any liability over such content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact us!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or the processing of your personal data, please contact us at apps.dmytrii.sinko@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last updated: 27 November 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solo - Time Tracking &amp; Invoicing</title>
      <link>https://apps.sinko.me/en/apps/solo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 22:13:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.sinko.me/en/apps/solo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.sinko.me&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&#34;img-responsive&#34; src=&#34;https://apps.sinko.me/images/download_on_appstore_en.svg&#34; title=&#34;Завантажити з AppStore&#34;&gt;
&lt;/a&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solo will be available shortly on AppStore!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/6giA-LFZt5g&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;
Solo is simple and efficient app for individual professionals who needs to track time and bill clients. Solo time tracker is focused on simplicity: no registration or any configuration required. Start working right away. Charge client in 3 taps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great features we believe you will like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Really simple history. You can see how much time you spend each day and how much money you earn. No complex charts. No tiny unreadable numbers. Everything is easy to read and analyze.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple timers running concurrently. You want to consult two clients and charge them separately? Maybe you are working with one client stuck in queue and have time to do some calls to help other client? We have that covered. With Solo time tracker you can have multiple timers running at the same time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast and simple controls. You can start timer or change invoice status with one swipe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add or edit time records. You can add time records or edit existing ones if you need. Actually you can generate whole invoice based on records you added manually (this required premium).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track invoice status. Be aware if invoice is paid or unpaid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handy notifications. Never forget to start tracking time. Solo will also remind about active timers so you do not forget to stop them when you need.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are even more features. Download Solo and try yourself!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>