<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terms-rsses on Sinko Apps</title>
    <link>https://apps.sinko.me/uk/terms/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terms-rsses on Sinko Apps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Дмитрій Сінько</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 13:20:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://apps.sinko.me/uk/terms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://apps.sinko.me/uk/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 13:20:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.sinko.me/uk/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Valid from 15/03/2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using our products and services (the “Service/s”). By becoming a member or using our Services you accept and agree to these Terms and Conditions (“Terms”). Therefore, it is important that you carefully read through these Terms. If you do not consent to these Terms, you should not use service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;using-our-services&#34;&gt;Using our Services&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may only use the Services as permitted by law and these Terms. By using our Services, you agree that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the personal data provided by you is accurate and up to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Violation of any of these Terms will lead to a direct termination of your user account and subscription. If you violate these terms, you will not get a refund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any criticism or feedback regarding Services, to firstly contact us to help us to improve our Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may not transmit, and/or distribute files that may damage our Services or others’ computers or property (such as viruses and trojan horses).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;premium&#34;&gt;Premium&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section only applies when you purchase and/or subscribe to Premium or other paid products. By paying the subscription fee you get access to Premium during the time your subscription is valid, subject to these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All subscriptions with Premium are paid in advance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may at any time terminate your membership, in which case your membership will still be valid for the subscription time you have already paid for. If you have subscribed to the Services through the use of App Store, Google Play Store, Amazon App Store or any other such service provider, using in-app purchase, you can only cancel your subscription through the use of their services. Subscription fees can be found in the mobile application. We accept a variety of different methods of payment, such as Apple iTunes. Special terms and conditions may apply. We reserve the right to change the subscription fees from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You hereby consent to start using the Services immediately upon subscribing with Premium or other paid products. All payments handled by Apple, such as in-app purchases, can only be refunded by Apple and with Apple’s consent. If you would like to contact Apple, please click &lt;a href=&#34;http://support.apple.com/kb/ht4098&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Default in payment shall not be deemed as a termination of a Premium subscription.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;intellectual-property&#34;&gt;Intellectual property&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All rights in and to the Services, including any trademarks, service marks, trade names and copyrighted content (collectively “Intellectual Property”) presented within the Service are the property of Dmytrii Sinko and/or third parties. You agree not to use Intellectual Property for any other purposes except for your use of the Service, unless required otherwise by applicable mandatory law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;disclaimer-and-limitation-of-liability&#34;&gt;Disclaimer and limitation of liability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You use the Service at your own risk. The Service is provided “AS IS”, without any warranties, and Dmytrii Sinko does not warrant that the Service and availability thereof will be uninterrupted or error free. Dmytrii Sinko does not assume any responsibility for errors or omissions in the information or software or other documents, including User Material, which are referenced by or linked to. References or links to third parties&amp;rsquo; websites are provided &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; without warranty of any kind, either express or implied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Dmytrii Sinko be liable for any indirect or consequential damages, except in cases of intentional misconduct or gross negligence. To the maximum extent permitted under applicable law, Dmytrii Sinko&amp;rsquo;s aggregated liability for any direct damages shall be limited to the lesser of: (i) membership fees paid by the user; (ii) membership fees paid by the user during the previous calendar month; or (iii) 100 UAH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;miscellaneous&#34;&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the sake of clarity, Dmytrii Sinko, doesn’t undertake the obligation to monitor the contents of User Material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are not entitled to assign your rights and/or obligations under these Terms or use of the Service to any third party without Dmytrii Sinko&amp;rsquo;s prior written consent. Dmytrii Sinko is entitled to assign its rights and/or obligations under these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dmytrii Sinko reserves the right to refuse the Service to anyone for any reason at any time. Dmytrii Sinko may revise these Terms from time to time and the most current version will always be posted on this website. Any and all material changes shall become into effect between you and Dmytrii Sinko upon your acceptance of such changes (e.g. by using the Services after such notification has been made to you or renewing your subscription).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governing law and dispute resolution
These Terms and the use of the Services are governed by the laws of Ukraine, except for its conflicts of laws principles. All claims arising out of or relating to these Terms or the Service shall be resolved by the public Ukrainian courts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact details
For further information, inquiries or assistance you may contact Dmytrii Sinko. Customer Service is available in ways specified on the website or in the apps. The channels for support might differ from time-to-time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you have any questions regarding this Terms and Conditions, please contact us at apps.dmytrii.sinko@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last updated: 15/03/2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>